Daniel Brzanov

Web designer & developer • Graphic designer • UI/UX designer

About me

Daniel Brzanov

Designer & developer delicon@proton.me 070 286 191 I am a versatile web and graphic designer as well as a web developer. I posses a unique combination of technical expertise and creative vision. My proficiency in tools such as **Photoshop**, **Illustrator**, and **Figma**, allows me to design visually stunning graphics, layouts, and user-friendly websites that are both functional and visually pleasing. I have a deep understanding of **HTML**, **CSS**, **JavaScript**, **PHP**, and **MySQL**, that allows me to code and implement those designs in a way that is both efficient and effective. I understand the importance of both **UI** and **UX** and I always strive to create a seamless user experience.

Experience

Studio Moderna

Lead designer 2023 - Present Responsible for creating and overseeing designs for all sales channels of the company.

- Printed materials, catalogues, posters, POS materials, flyers etc.
- Materials for digital advertising

Studio Moderna

Digital designer, web developer 2007 - 2022 Working on a projects and materials for internet sales channel.

- Website and landing page design and development
- Advertising materials and content for multiple platforms

Vivde, Norway

Web developer SEO specialist 2022 - Present Developing web sites and optimize them for modern search engines.

Frelance

Designer & developer 2007 - Present

Creating and optimizing websites, landing pages, SEO, web server management, digital advertising materials, print materials such as posters, flyers, catalogues, billboards.

Education

Alexandria Academy

2005-2006

Alexandria is the oldest private educational institution, specializing in education in the field of IT and applied arts.

Wordpress

MySQL

SEO

- Web design & development
- Graphic design

I know

Photoshop UI/UX
Illustrator HTML
InDesign CSS
Figma JavaScript
WebFlow PHP

JavaScript Web Server Management

PHP WiX